# Buğra Keskin

## DevOps Engineer

🔀 bugra.keskin@gmail.com 📞 +905547624468 💡 Muğla, Türkiye 🔭 www.bugra-keskin.com

#### **PROFILE**

A highly analytical, solution-oriented, resourceful applicant who has extensive knowledge in network administration, providing the server support and the application support. Demonstrated capability to deliver creative relevant server and application strategies by way of all-encompassing problem-solving skills. Expertise in troubleshooting and administration for all Microsoft operating systems and many Linux Operating Systems.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

**DevOps System Admin** 

KubixCloud Administration of the IT infrastructure

Choosing the right deployment models

Conducting the testing protocol and critical monitoring

Automation of repetitive tasks

Provide the server support and the application support

Ensure that the backup is sufficient, and if there isn't any adequate backup, then you have to create a backup policy as well.

**Operations Manager** 

2018 - 08/2022 Muğla, Türkiye GM-Informatics *⊘* 

I am responsible of all operations between contracted firms and internal management systems.

Responsible for approximately 850 assets of IT infrastructure.

Leading new technologies and projects.

**Information Technologies Expert** 

Zeniva Resort Hotels Muğla, Türkiye

I was responsible for 4 hotels which are located in near peninsula. I worked a full month and resign because the hotels are too far and transportation is problematic.

Information Technologies Manager

BH Prestii Muğla, Türkiye

I was responsible for 3 hotels. I created a VPN connection between the hotels and manage it for the PMS. Also created a new captive portal wireless system for guests.

**Information Technologies Manager** 

Swiss Hotel Muğla, Türkiye

I worked as a pre-opening technology team manager.

**Information Technologies Manager** 

Kefaluka Resort HOTEL

High-quality, customer-oriented, professional service responsibilities I work and support as part of a successful team. Internal support to staff and I provide the highest level of guest service.

Information Technologies Supervisor

**YachtWORKS** 

Maintenance and operation of ships serving 3rd party software applications running on the

server to be backed up and carried out maintenance.

Information Technologies Supervisor

ANB Resort HOTEL Muğla, Türkiye

First time as an IT Supervisor working in a hotel. Hotel has 3 server setup. Maintenance of the PC and Servers. Helping guests to use internet. ... there is more and i will gladly share if

asked.

Harju maakond, Estonia

08/2022 - present

2018 - 2018

2016 - 2017

2015 - 2015

2011 - 2015

Muğla, Türkiye

2010 - 2011

Muğla, Türkiye

2005 - 2008

#### **PROJECTS**

#### **BODTO Documentation Portal**

2021 - 2021

With the help of open-source community.

Created NC server for the company.

#### GM Informatics KVK 2020 – present

Document Management Portal

I created a document management system for the KVK.

## Kefaluka Wifi Project 2014 – 2014

Wifi coverage boosted for the hotel.

The hotel sits on 20 acres and one big connected building. I and my team was able to build a wifi coverage of all areas within the hotel

#### **SKILLS**

#### Strong problem solver

## Team player

#### Good time management

#### **Effective communication**

#### **Zabbix Monitoring**

Monitoring whole infrastructure with various alerting systems

#### MongoDB/MySQL/MariaDB/PostgreSQL

Managing and securing database operations as well as backing up and recovery operations.

#### **Backup solutions Expert**

Tested and used lots of backup solutions

#### Static Web page developer

Can do small and mid projects

#### Design and implement database structures

#### Microsoft Server 2012-2019

Managing windows server environment

#### Lead and deliver complex software systems

Many new technologies is waiting to be discovered

## **LANGUAGES**

## English

B2 - Highly proficient in speaking and writing

## **INTERESTS**

Playing Basketball | Watching movies | Travelling

## **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor of Business** 

Anadolu University

Science & Math degree

Marmara Private High School

2004 – 2014 Istanbul, Türkiye

1988 – 1999 Istanbul, Türkiye